Guide to the Poly Archives Historic Photograph Collection RG.026
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Poly Archives Historic Photograph Collection
1857-2011
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
Polytechnic Institute of New York University
RG.026
35 Linear Feet 23 boxes
This collection of photographs and negatives documents the history of Polytechnic from 1857 to 2011.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged, by subject, into eight series:
Series I: Buildings and Campus Views Series II: Academics Series III: Administration Series IV: Publications and Productions Series V: Series Series VI: Alumni Series VII: Events Series VIII: Miscellaneous
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research without restrictions.
Biographical / Historical
The images in this collection include unprocessed photographs and negatives in the Poly Archives as well as images transferred to the archives from various departments over a number of years. Some of these departments include: Alumni Relations, Development, Student Activities, Public Relations, and the President's Office.
Scope and Contents
The photographs and negatives in this collection depict the Polytechnic campus, departments, labs, students, faculty, staff, administration, alumni, and notable events. Spanning 1857 to 2011, the images cover the school's physical and administrative changes from the Brooklyn Collegiate and Polytechnic Institute to the Polytechnic Institute of Brooklyn, to the Polytechnic Institute of New York, to Polytechnic University to, finally, the Polytechnic Institute of New York University.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials found in collection; there is no documentation concerning the provenance of these materials.
Photographs; Photography negatives; Polytechnic Institute of New York University
- Series I: Buildings and Campus Views
  - Subseries A: Brooklyn
    - 189 Washington Street- Brooklyn Juvenile High School, undated; cuid0 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Polytechnic in 1857 (Reproduction), undated; cuid1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 69 Schermerhorn Street & Quonset Hut, undated; cuid2 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 69 Schermerhorn Street negatives, undated; cuid3 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 85 Livingston Street, Gymnasium, undated; cuid4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 85 Livingston, Exterior, 1900-1940; cuid5 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 85 Livingston Street Fire, 1938; cuid6 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 85 Livingston Street negatives, undated; cuid7 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 85 Livingston Street & 99 Livingston Street, 1900-1953; cuid8 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 85 Livingston & 99 Livingston Street, Student Lounges, 1920-1957; cuid9 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 85 Livingston Street & 99 Livingston Street, Departmental Libararies (English, Chemical Engineering, and Mechanical Engineering), circa 1919; cuid10 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 94 Livingston Street, undated; cuid11 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 94 Livingston Street negatives, undated; cuid12 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 99 Livingston Street, Exterior, 1880-1927; cuid13 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 99 Livingston Street Buildings negatives, undated; cuid14 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 99 Livingston Street, Interior of Spicer Library, undated; cuid15 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 99 Livingston Street, Oversize Photo, 1890; cuid16 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - 99 Livingston Street, Stained Glass Window, undated; cuid17 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 99 Livingston Street, Interior, 1948-1957; cuid18 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Livingston Street Campus, Classrooms, 1920-1922; cuid19 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Move from Livingston Street to Jay Street, 1955-1958; cuid20 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Pearl Street Building, undated; cuid21 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Hillman Building, undated; x (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Livingston Street Campus, Demolition of Buildings, undated; cuid22 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 333 Jay Street, Before Polytechnic, 1950-1957; cuid23 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 333 Jay Street Entrance Exterior, Early Views (1950s-1960s), 1950-1960; cuid24 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 333 Jay Street Entrance Exterior, 1960s-1970s, 1954-1972; cuid25 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 333 Jay Street Entrance Exterior, 1973-1985, cuid26 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 333 Jay Street Entrance Exterior, 1985-2002, cuid27 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 333 Jay Street Entrance, Viewed from City Park (Site of Brooklyn Marriott), 1950-1972; cuid28 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 333 Jay Street/6 MetroTech Center, Entrance Exterior 2002-2008, cuid29 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 333 Jay Street, Rogers Hall, undated; cuid30 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 333 Jay Street Negatives, undated; cuid31 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 333 Jay Street, Views with Myrtle Avenue Elevated Train, 1959-1969; cuid32 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 333 Jay Street, Campus Interiors, undated; cuid33 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 333 Jay Street Interior, Student Lounges in Rogers Hall, before 2000; cuid34 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 333 Jay Street Interior, Library, undated; cuid35 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 333 Jay Street Interior, Cafeteria, before 2000; cuid36 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 333 Jay Street Interior, Jasper Kane Cafeteria, after 2000; cuid37 (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Jay Street Campus, Jacobs Academic Building Construction Proposal, undated; cuid38 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Jay Street Campus, Othmer Dorm Construction Proposal, circa 2000; cuid39 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Jay Street Campus, Jacobs Academic Building & Othmer Dorm Construction Negatives, undated; cuid40 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Jay Street Campus, Proposed Academic Tower, circa 1960; cuid41 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Jay Street Campus, Proposed Physical Plant, 1965 February 6; cuid42 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Jay Street Campus, Artist Renderings for Proposed Renovations, circa 1960; cuid43 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Jay Street Campus Interior Views, Classrooms, undated; cuid44 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Jay Street Campus Slides, undated; cuid45 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Jay Street Campus, Images in Downtown Transformed exhibit at Brooklyn Historical Society, 2000; cuid46 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Buildings Around MetroTech Center, after 1990; cuid47 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - MetroTech Commons Aerial View, undated; cuid48 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - MetroTech Campus, Polytechnic banners, 1999 September; cuid49 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - 5 MetroTech Center, Dibner Library/CATT Building, undated; cuid50 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - 5 MetroTech Center, Dibner Library/CATT Building Construction, undated; cuid51 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - 5 Metrotech Center, Dibner Library/CATT Building OVERSIZE, circa 1992; cuid52 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - 5 MetroTech Center, Building Upgrade, 1998; cuid53 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - 6 MetroTech Center, Jacobs Academic Building Construction, undated; cuid54 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - 6 MetroTech Center, Jacobs Academic Building Entrance Interior, 2002-2008; cuid55 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - 6 MetroTech Center, Jacobs Academic Building Interior- Classrooms and Labs, after 2002; cuid56 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - 6 MetroTech Center, Jacobs Academic Building Interior- Gymnasium, after 2002; cuid57 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - 305-315 Jay Street, Jacobs Administration Building, 1950s to 1990s; cuid58 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - 365-367 Jay Street, Jay Street Firehouse, undated; cuid59 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - 311 Bridge Street, Wunsch Hall, undated; cuid60 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - 311 Bridge Street, Wunsch Student Center, 1996; cuid61 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Wunsch Center, 1996 October 25; cuid62 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Bridge Street & Johnson Street, Nichols Hall, undated; cuid63 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - 55 Johnson Street, Microwave Research Institute (MRI) Building, undated; cuid64 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - 101 Johnson Street, Othmer Dorm, circa 2000; cuid65 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - 101 Johnson Street, Othmer Dorm Construction, undated; cuid66 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Admin Council, Jacobs Building Tour, 2001 September 26; cuid67 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Admin Council, Jacobs Building Tour, 2001 October 29; cuid68 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Balanced Cylinders Mock-up (MetroTech), 2002 February 27; cuid69 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Views of Downtown Brooklyn, 1937; undated; cuid70 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Views of Brooklyn Bridge and Lower Manhattan, 1993; cuid71 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Views of Downtown Brooklyn, Negatives, undated; cuid72 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Subseries B: Bronx
    - NYU Bronx, University Heights Campus Exterior, undated; cuid73 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - NYU Bronx, University Heights Campus Aerial Views, undated; cuid74 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - NYU Bronx, University Heights Campus- United States National Army Training Detachment & ROTC, 1919-1940; cuid75 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - NYU Bronx, University Heights Campus- History, undated; cuid76 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - NYU Bronx, University Heights Campus, Interior & People, undated; cuid77 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - NYU Bronx, University Heights Campus- Negatives, undated; cuid78 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Subseries C: Long Island
    - Long Island Campus, Freeport Buildings Construction, undated; cuid79 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Long Island Campus, Freeport Buildings Exterior, undated; cuid80 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Long Island Campus, Freeport Lab Design, undated; cuid81 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Long Island Campus, Freeport Interior- Classrooms & Labs, undated; cuid82 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Long Island Campus, Freeport Negatives, undated; cuid83 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Long Island Campus Slides, undated; cuid84 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Plans & Signing, undated; cuid85 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Groundbreaking & Construction, undated; cuid86 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Exterior and Athletic Dome, undated; cuid87 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Entrance Exterior, undated; cuid88 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Entrance Exterior OVERSIZE, undated; cuid89 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Interior and Classrooms, undated; cuid90 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Dorms, undated; cuid91 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Library, undated; cuid92 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Maps, undated; cuid93 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Commencement, undated; cuid94 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Events and Symposia, undated; cuid95 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Opening & Dedication Ceremony, undated; cuid96 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Dedication Letters and Speech, 1962; cuid97 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Bassett Research Lab, 1966; cuid98 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Bassett Research Lab Dedication, 1966; cuid99 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Bassett Research Lab Dedication Ceremony, 1966; cuid100 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Bassett Research Lab Dedication Ceremony, 1966; cuid101 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Bassett Research and Aerospace Lab, undated; cuid102 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Wind Tunnel, undated; cuid103 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Laser Research Lab of the Electrophysics Group of the MRI, undated; cuid104 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Negatives, undated; cuid105 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale 'Take the Next Step Dinner', 1993; cuid106 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Etiquette Seminar, undated; cuid107 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Ivan Frisch Pictures, 2001; cuid108 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Building & Interior, 2002; cuid109 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale September 20, 2002 Event, cuid110 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Graduate Center, undated; cuid111 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Long Island Campus, Farmingdale Graduate Center Pictures OVERSIZE, cuid112 (Box 23)
  - Subseries D: Miscellaneous
    - 20th Avenue Subway (N Line) Construction, 1953; cuid113 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Air Trolley, undated; cuid114 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - George Washington Bridge, 1965; cuid115 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Marriott, 1999 April 13; cuid116 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Metro Cafe & Bookstore Ribbon Cutting, 1997 October 1; cuid117 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Surveying Fort Greene Park, 1951; cuid118 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Westchester Campus, undated; cuid119 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Worthington Hydraulic Works, Harrison, NJ, undated; cuid120 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Series II: Academics
  - Subseries A: Departments and Laboratories
    - Aerospace Department- Long Island Campus, Farmingdale, undated; cuid121 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Aerospace Lab- Farmingdale, Long Island, undated; cuid122 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Aerospace Lab- Farmingdale, Long Island, undated; cuid123 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Aerospace Lab- Freeport, Long Island, undated; cuid124 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Biochemistry Lab, 1979; cuid125 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Bioengineering Lab, undated; cuid126 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Biomedical Engineering Department, 2000; cuid127 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Chemical Engineering Department, 1954-2005; cuid128 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Chemical Engineering Lab, 1930s - 1990s; cuid129 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Chemistry Department, 1955; cuid130 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Chemistry Faculty, undated; cuid131 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Chemistry Lab, undated; cuid132 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Chemistry Lab, undated; cuid133 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Chemistry Lab, 1999; cuid134 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Civil Engineering Department, 1954-1955; cuid135 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Civil Engineering Lab, undated; cuid136 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Civil Engineering Summer Camp- Greene Engineering Camp, 1959 Summer; cuid137 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Combustion Lab, 1928; cuid138 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Computer Aided Design (CAD) Lab, undated; cuid139 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Computer Science Lab, undated; cuid140 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Computer Science Lab, 2001 May 24; cuid141 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - David Conklin Lab, 1999 January; cuid142 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Early Chemistry Lab, circa 1920s; cuid143 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Early Mechanical Engineering Lab, undated; cuid144 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Economics Department, 1954-1955; cuid145 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Electrical and Computer Engineering Lab, undated; cuid146 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Electrical and Electromagnetic Engineering Lab, undated; cuid147 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Electrical Engineering Department, 1955-1986; cuid148 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Electrical Engineering Department, Electric Car (1996), cuid149 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Electrical Engineering Lab, undated; cuid150 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Electrical Engineering Lab 1930s-1950s, 1930-1950; cuid151 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Electron Microscope, undated; cuid152 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Electrophysics Engineering- Laser Lab, undated; cuid153 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Electrophysics Engineering- Plasma Lab, undated; cuid154 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - English Department, 1955; cuid155 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - General Lab Pictures, undated; cuid156 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Glass Blowing Lab, undated; cuid157 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Helicopter - Mechanical Engineering Lab, 1971; cuid158 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - IBM Data Processing Lab, 1964 January 10; cuid159 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Ice Project- X-Ray Diffraction Studies of an Ice Crystal, undated; cuid160 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Industry Research Associates, undated; cuid161 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Interdisciplinary Lab, 2000 October 13; cuid162 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Interdisciplinary Writing Program, 1997-1998; cuid163 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Jet Propulsion Lab, 1962 November 6; cuid164 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Junior Circuits Lab- Lie Detector, undated; cuid165 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Lab Equipment, undated; cuid166 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Language Department, 1954-1955; cuid167 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Language Lab, undated; cuid168 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Life Sciences Lab, undated; cuid169 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Macro Camera Lab, undated; cuid170 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Magnet Lab, undated; cuid171 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Mathematics Department, undated; cuid172 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Mechanical Engineering Department, 1955; cuid173 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Mechanical Engineering Lab, undated; cuid174 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Mechanical Engineering Lab- Drafting Room, Livingston Street, undated; cuid175 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Metallurgical Engineering Department, 1955; cuid176 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Metallurgical Engineering Lab, undated; cuid177 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Metallurgy, 1989; cuid178 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Microwave Lab- Farmingdale, undated; cuid179 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous Labs, undated; cuid180 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Labs, undated; cuid181 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Labs, undated; cuid182 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Miscellaneous Students in Lab, undated; cuid183 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Physical Education Department, 1955; cuid184 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Physics Department, undated; cuid185 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Physics Lab, undated; cuid186 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Polymeric Materials Lab, undated; cuid187 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Potts Physics Lab, circa 1920; cuid188 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Psychology Lab, circa 1960; cuid189 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Robotics Lab, undated; cuid190 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Shellac Research Bureau, undated; cuid191 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Shock Tube Lab, undated; cuid192 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Social Sciences Department, undated; cuid193 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Social Sciences Lab, undated; cuid194 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Transportation Planning Lab, undated; cuid195 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Various Early Labs, circa 1920; cuid196 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Various Faculty in Lab, undated; cuid197 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Various Unknown Labs, undated; cuid198 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Vortex Augmentor Lab, undated; cuid199 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - X-Ray Diffraction Lab, undated; cuid200 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Subseries B: Scholarships and Awards
    - DeGaeta Scholarship Lunch, 1997 January 27; cuid201 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Excellence In Polymer Science Award, undated; cuid202 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Grumman Students Awards Lunch, 1985; cuid203 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - International Telephone & Telegraph, 1960; cuid204 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Lemelson Scholars, 2000; cuid205 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Lemelson Scholarship Induction 2000, 2000 March 13; cuid206 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Northeastern Chemical Association $40k Scholarship Fund, 2002 January 23; cuid207 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 1995, 1995 December 6; cuid208 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 1998, 1998 May 21; cuid209 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Lunch 1999, 1999 November 30; cuid210 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 1999, 1999 May 27; cuid211 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Lunch 2000, 2000 November 21; cuid212 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 2000, 2000 May 18; cuid213 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 2000, 2000 May 18; cuid214 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 2001, 2001 November 20; cuid215 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 2002, 2002 May 22; cuid216 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 2002, 2002 May 22; cuid217 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 2002- Dedication, 2002 May 22; cuid218 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 2002- Negatives, 2002 May 22; cuid219 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Lunch 2003, 2003 November; cuid220 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 2003, 2003 May 21; cuid221 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Dinner 2005, 2005 May 17; cuid222 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Poly 100 Scholarship Newsletter, undated; cuid223 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - President's Service Awards 1986, 1986 May; cuid224 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - President's Service Awards 1987, cuid225 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - President's Service Awards 1995, 1995 November 9; cuid226 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - President's Service Awards 1997, 1997 May 1; cuid227 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - President's Service Awards 1998, 1998 May 16; cuid228 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - President's Service Awards 1999, 1999 May 24; cuid229 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - President's Service Awards 2001, 2001 May 2; cuid230 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - President's Service Awards 2002, 2002 October 23; cuid231 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - President's Service Awards Miscellaneous, undated; cuid232 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Principal's Scholars Dinner 1997, 1997 December 11; cuid233 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Principal's Scholars Dinner 1999, 1999 March 10; cuid234 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Promise Fund Board Members, 2002; cuid235 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 1988, 1990, cuid236 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 1994, 1994 March 23; cuid237 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 1995, 1995 June 28; cuid238 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 1996, 1996 March 19; cuid239 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 1996- California, 1996 October; cuid240 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 1997, 1997 June 25; cuid241 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 1998, 1998 June 24; cuid242 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 1998, 1998 June 24; cuid243 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 1999, 1999 May 20; cuid244 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 1999, 1999 May 20; cuid245 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2000, 2000 June 22; cuid246 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2001, 2001 June 12; cuid247 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2001, 2001 June 12; cuid248 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2002, 2002 June 11; cuid249 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2002, 2002 June 11; cuid250 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2002, 2002 June 11; cuid251 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2003, 2003 June 26; cuid252 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2004, 2004 June 22; cuid253 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2005, 2005 June 21; cuid254 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2005, 2005 June 21; cuid255 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2005, 2005 June 21; cuid256 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Promise Fund Dinner 2006, 2006 September 15; cuid257 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Promise Fund Induction 2000, 2000 January 28; cuid258 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Promise Fund Induction 2001, 2001 January 31; cuid259 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Promise Fund Induction 2002, 2002 January 31; cuid260 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Promise Fund Induction 2003, 2003 January 30; cuid261 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Promise Fund Induction 2004, 2004 January 29; cuid262 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Promise Fund Induction 2005, 2005 January 31; cuid263 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Promise Fund Newsletter 1996, cuid264 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Promise Fund Newsletter 1997, cuid265 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Promise Fund Newsletter 1998, cuid266 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Promise Fund Newsletter 2000, 2000 January; cuid267 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Promise Fund Newsletter 2001, cuid268 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Promise Fund Newsletter 2005, cuid269 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Promise Fund Newsletter 2006, cuid270 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Promise Fund Scholars Spring 2000, 2000 January; cuid271 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Promise Fund Scholars Spring 2001, 2001 Spring; cuid272 (Box 8, Folder 5)